Hello everyone, today we will introduce you to a copy window.
First, let's open the copy window.
Please load a copy from the library window.
Drag the copy file to the copy window to load it as a copy type.
Drag the appropriate copy type to the costume.
Please press Ctrl-C, Ctrl-V to copy and paste the copy.
You can change the style of these copies through the copy window.
After selecting a copy type, you can modify the details of this copy type type by selecting a copy type.
These modifications will also work on all the copies of this type.
Please see the description for instructions.
You can choose to open the Preserve option in the property of the component type to load or save the component style.
This is the introduction of the component window. Thank you for watching.